Edwin B. Rollins Papers MS054
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1850 -- 1961; 1930 -- 1955; MS054.003; 0.5 Linear Feet; 565 Digital Object(s)
  - Views southwest from Ballou Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02362; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Views southeast from Ballou Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02363; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southwest from the Rez, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02364; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Campus recreation field, 1884; MS054.003.DO.02365; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southwest from Ballou Hall, 1877; MS054.003.DO.02366; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southwest from Ballou Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02367; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - West Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02368; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Metcalf Hall, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02369; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Old university Post Office, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02370; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Post offices; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - President's House, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02371; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1886; MS054.003.DO.02372; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Greenhouse at Bowen Gate, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02373; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Gates; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Stratton Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02374; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Braker Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02375; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - North side of Ballou Hall, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02376; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Miner and Paige Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02377; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Carmichael Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02378; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Railroad station, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02379; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Richardson House, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02380; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Hodgdon Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02382; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Cousens Gymnasium, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02383; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Gymnasiums; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Power House, 1854; MS054.003.DO.02384; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Barnum Museum, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02385; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Museums; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Goddard Hall, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02386; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Interior of the Tufts post office, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02387; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Building"
  - Pearson Chemical Laboratory, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02388; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Hall, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02389; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Carmichael Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02390; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Sweet Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02391; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Academic; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Reserve Officers Training Corps
  - Carmichael Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02392; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Hodgdon Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02393; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Talbot Avenue, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02394; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02395; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Fletcher Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02396; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - North Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02397; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; AMRAD
  - Support beams for Miller Hall, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02398; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - First West Hall, 1857; MS054.003.DO.02399; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Bush Hall, 1959; MS054.003.DO.02400; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Anderson and Robinson Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02401; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Bray Laboratory for the Mechanical Engineering Department, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02402; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Anderson Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02403; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Rear of Robinson and Anderson Halls, November, 1960; MS054.003.DO.02404; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Packard and East Halls from Ballou Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02405; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of West Hall from The Rez, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02406; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Setting-up of seats for Class Day activities, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02407; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    box: "Slides and negatives from Prof Rollins. Donated September 1967"
  - Decorations on Ballou Hall for Class Day celebrations, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02408; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    "Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967"
    Events; Class Day; Buildings; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Decorations on Ballou Hall for Class Day celebrations, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02409; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Lanterns along Ballou walk for Class Day celebrations, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02410; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    box: "Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967"
  - Alumni field day, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02411; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Alumni and alumnae; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Class Day crowd seated, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02412; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Looking from Ballou Hall toward Goddard Gymnasium, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02413; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    box: Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967"
  - Looking from Ballou Hall toward Goddard Gymnasium, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02414; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Marsh views from #6 West Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02415; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Seniors at Class Day, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02416; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Robinson Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02417; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Curtis Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02418; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Barnum Hall, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02419; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Jumbo in the Barnum Museum, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02420; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Museums; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Room in Barnum Museum of Natural History, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02421; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Museums; Rooms; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Lecture room in Barnum Hall, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02422; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The Aritficial, 1956; MS054.003.DO.02423; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Iceskating on the Artificial, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02424; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The Artificial, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02425; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Alumnae Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02426; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Halls; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Alumni Association
  - Bush Hall, 1960; MS054.003.DO.02427; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Walk from Ballou Hall to Dearborn Gate, MS054.003.DO.02428; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Views from top of Ballou Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02429; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Views from top of Ballou Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02430; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Slides and negatives from Profs. Rollins. Donated September 1967."
  - View from the top of Ballou Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02431; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View from the top of Ballou Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02432; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View from the top of Ballou Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02433; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View from the top of Ballou Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02434; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Braker Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02435; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Construction of Bush Hall, 1959; MS054.003.DO.02436; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unidentified construction worker on third floor of Bush Hall, 1959; MS054.003.DO.02437; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Construction of Bush Hall, 1959; MS054.003.DO.02438; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Construction of first two floors of Bush Hall, 1959; MS054.003.DO.02439; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Carpentry shop in Bromfield-Pearson Building, 1904; MS054.003.DO.02440; Stebbins, N.L.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Rooms; Academic; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - The forge shop in Bromfield-Pearson, 1904; MS054.003.DO.02441; Stebbins, N.L.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    credited to Rollins, box: "Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967."
  - Exterior of Bromfield-Pearson, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02442; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of President Ballou's house in its orginal position, 1850; MS054.003.DO.02443; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Bonfire near the Gate House, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02444; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Billboard cartoon taken from Tufts Weekly, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02445; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Tufts Weekly
  - South corner view of Bray Laboratory, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02448; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Capen House from the east, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02449; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Carmichael Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02450; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of college from Powder House, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02451; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Lecture room in Old Chemical Laboratory, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02452; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Cohen Arts Center, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02453; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Professor Amos Dolbear, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02454; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Dolbear, Amos Emerson
  - Professor Amos Dolbear, 1885; MS054.003.DO.02455; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Professor Amos Dolmear, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02456; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of College Hill from accross the Artificial, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02457; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated Septmeber 1967."
  - View of campus from accross the Artificial, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02458; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The College Bell, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02459; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Bells; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Concordia, the new bell in the tower of Goddard Chapel, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02460; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Hand bell, MS054.003.DO.02461; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Chapel bells, MS054.003.DO.02462; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of brickyard behind the Old Chemistry Laboratory, 1899; MS054.003.DO.02463; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Views of campus from Powder House, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02464; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Two unidentified women standing before fence along College Avenue with College Hill in background, 1886; MS054.003.DO.02465; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of campus from Powder House, 1871; MS054.003.DO.02466; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of "Dog Cart" situated beside Curtis Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02467; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; copy negative
  - View of College Avenue, 1948; MS054.003.DO.02468; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of College Avenue, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02469; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Inside the tent on Class Day, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02470; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Views from campus accross Manning property, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02471; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Walkway from Dearborn Gate during Class Day, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02472; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Eaton Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02473; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Libraries; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Library
  - Cross on Goddard Chapel, Spring, 1933; MS054.003.DO.02474; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Architect's studies for the a new engineering building, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02475; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Models (representations); Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Plan for the building of a new engineering building, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02476; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Plan for the new engineering building, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02477; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - New plan for engineering buildings, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02478; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Memorial Steps, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02479; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Dearborn Gate, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02480; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Alumni Gate, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02481; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Hodgdon Gate, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02482; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Starkweather Gate, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02483; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Gager Gate, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02484; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Field house, MS054.003.DO.02485; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Fay Map of Tufts College, MS054.003.DO.02486; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Maps; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Dolbear House, MS054.003.DO.02487; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Office of the Music Department in Goddard Hall, MS054.003.DO.02488; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Departments; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Department of Music
  - Baseball cage in Goddard Hall, MS054.003.DO.02489; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Baseball cage; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Baseball
  - Dance floor in Goddard Hall, MS054.003.DO.02490; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Interior of Goddard Gymnasium, MS054.003.DO.02491; Stebbins, N.L.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Gymnasiums; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Switchboard for campus, MS054.003.DO.02492; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Switchboard; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Goddard Gym, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02493; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unidentified man sitting in glider, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02494; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Students helping glider in flight, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02495; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unfinished exterior of Goddard Chapel, 1883; MS054.003.DO.02496; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1883; MS054.003.DO.02497; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Taberna, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02517; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Taberna, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02518; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Stratton Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02519; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Delta Upsilon letters, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02520; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    box: Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967."
    Events; Winter Carnival; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Delta Upsilon
  - Snow sculpture of Jumbo for Zeta Psi, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02521; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Zeta Psi
  - Paige Hall's snow sculpture of Jack-in-the-Box, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02522; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    box: "Slides and negatives from Professor Rollins. Donated September 1967."
    Events; Winter Carnival; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Metcalf-East's snow sculpture of Peter Rabbit, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02523; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Off Hill Council's snow sculpture of Pinnochio, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02524; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Off Hill Council
  - Off Hill Council's snow sculpture of Pinnochio, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02525; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Theta Delta Chi's snow sculpture of a "Drinking Party,", 1950; MS054.003.DO.02526; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Theta Delta Chi
  - Off Hill Council's snow sculpture of Pinnochio, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02527; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - East Hall's snow sculpture of Cinderella, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02528; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Metcalf-West's snow sculpture of "Time Out,", 1950; MS054.003.DO.02529; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Capen House's snow sculpture of a pig, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02530; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Richardson's snow sculpture of a St. Bernard dog, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02531; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Richardson House's snow sculpture of a St. Bernard, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02532; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Dean Hall's snow sculpture of Goddard Chapel, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02533; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - East Hall's snow sculpture of Cinderella, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02534; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Students standing beside Zeta Psi's snow sculpture of Jumbo, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02535; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; People; Students; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Zeta Psi
  - Theta Delta Chi's snow sculpture of "Drinking Party,", 1950; MS054.003.DO.02536; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Phi Delta's snow sculpture of a "Snow Devil,", 1950; MS054.003.DO.02537; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Phi Delta
  - Zeta Psi's snow sculpture of Jumbo, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02538; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Delta Upsilon's snow sculpture of a lighthouse, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02539; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; copy negative; Delta Upsilon
  - Dean Hall's snow sculpture of Goddard Chapel, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02540; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Events; Winter Carnival; copy negative
  - View of exterior of the President's House from the back, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02541; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Buildings; Houses; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of exterior of the President's House from the back, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02542; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Jackson Gymnasium, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02543; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Metcalf Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02544; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of skull, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02548; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of an elf with a beer mug, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02549; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Humpty-Dumpty, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02550; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Jumbo with cake celebrating Tufts' centennial, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02551; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of boy wistling, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02552; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculptures of boy and women, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02553; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of boy in bath tub, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02554; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Jumbo, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02555; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Pinnochio, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02556; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of a train engine, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02557; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of boy climbing into a mug of beer, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02558; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Jumbo and birthday cake celebrating Tufts' centennial, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02559; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of two animals embracing, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02560; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of boy in bathtub, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02561; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of old man celebrating Tufts' centennial, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02562; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of a clown, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02563; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture with Pogo and child going down a slide, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02564; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of skull, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02565; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of boy whistling, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02566; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of elf with a beer mug, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02567; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of "The Thinker,", 1952; MS054.003.DO.02568; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of boy whistling, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02569; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of "The Thinker,", 1952; MS054.003.DO.02570; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of elf with beer mug, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02571; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of a boy in a bathtub, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02572; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of old man symbolizing Tufts' centennial, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02573; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of "The Thinker,", 1952; MS054.003.DO.02574; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of "The Old Woman who Lived in a Shoe,", 1952; MS054.003.DO.02575; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of a clown, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02576; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Snow sculpture of Jumbo and a birthday cake celebrating Tufts' centennial, 1952; MS054.003.DO.02577; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Pearson Chemical Laboratory on Tufts campus, 1957; MS054.003.DO.02578; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Bouve-Boston School of Physical Education, 1957; MS054.003.DO.02579; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - Heating plant, 1958; MS054.003.DO.02580; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - New boiler room, 1957; MS054.003.DO.02581; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Miner Hall, 1925; MS054.003.DO.02582; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117, Box Shared 29)
    box: "Slides and negatives from Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967."; image contained in Light on the Hill, p. 202.
    Buildings; Academic; photographic print; photographic print; Crane Theological School
  - Theological chapel in Paige Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02583; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Chapels; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; Interior views; copy negative
  - Amrad mast near North Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02584; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Radio Stations; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; AMRAD
  - View toward the west of Amrad mast, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02585; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of North Hall from near East Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02586; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Sweet Hall housing Tufts' R.O.T.C. program, 1953; MS054.003.DO.02587; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Sweet Hall, 1953; MS054.003.DO.02588; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Systems building, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02589; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Systems building, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02590; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unidentified men painting bleachers, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02591; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Tufts Oval, 1902 -- 1905; MS054.003.DO.02592; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Front view of shelter at Tufts College railroad station, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02593; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Railroad stations; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Front view of Tufts College railroad station, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02594; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Engine room in Tufts' power house, 1905; MS054.003.DO.02595; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)